Hi. My name is Andrew Pastor,
你好 我是 Andrew Pastor
and I am a Content Developer for the Intro to Self-Driving Car Nanodegree.
负责无人驾驶入门的内容开发
In this lesson, C++ Intro to Optimization,
在本课中 C ++ 优化介绍
and the following lesson,
和之后的课程中
C++ Optimization Practice, you'll
C ++优化实践
be using a feature of the classroom that you haven't seen yet.
你将使用你之前没有看到的教室功能
When you go to the next part of the lesson,
当你进入本课的下一部分时
an embedded command line tool will load that looks like this.
一个嵌入的命令行工具将被加载 看起来就像这样
Usually, when you use a computer,
通常 当你使用电脑时
you're using your mouse in a graphical user interface to move files around,
你是在图形用户界面中使用鼠标移动文件
open files, create new files, and open programs.
打开文件 创建新文件和打开程序
But there's another way that you can use your computer,
但还有另外一种使用电脑的方式
and this is with the keyboard and entering commands directly to the computer.
使用键盘 直接在计算机上输入命令
So, this is essentially what we've set up for you in the classroom.
所以 这实际上就是我们在课堂上为你设定的环境
When you open this,
当你打开这个
this section of the classroom is actually connecting to
这部分课堂实际上是连接着
a remote computer that contains files and allows you to run your C++ programs.
一个包含文件并允许你运行C ++程序的远程计算机
So, I wanted to give you an overview of what all of this is and how it works.
接下来 我想给大家介绍一下这是什么以及它是如何工作的
On a Mac or on a Linux machine,
在 Mac 或 Linux 机器上
there's a program called the Terminal that
有一个叫做终端 (Terminal) 的程序
allows you to do the same types of things that we're going to do here,
允许你做同样的事情 和我们要在这里做的事一样
and the equivalent in Windows is called the Console Window.
和 Windows 中被称为控制台窗口 (console window)
So, when you go to the next part of the lesson,
当你进入下一课时
Demo Machine Code, this is going to open.
演示:机器码 你就会看到
And you'll see there are three big sections
有三个大的板块
plus a menu down here and then this menu up here.
一个菜单在这里 然后这个菜单在这里
The menu up here is just to be able to navigate
这里的菜单只是为了能够浏览
the classroom which you should already be familiar with.
你应该已经非常熟悉的教室
This part here is showing you all of the files that are on this remote computer.
这部分显示了远程计算机上的所有文件
So, you can see that because we're in the demo machine code part of the lesson,
所以 你可以看到 因为我们在本课程的演示机器代码部分
we've automatically set it up that it goes to the folder,
我们已经自动设置它到文件夹
demo_machine_code, and has these two files in it,
demo_machine_code 里面有这两个文件
which are opening automatically for you.
它们会自动为你打开
But you can actually navigate through this with your mouse and see workspace,
但实际上你可以用鼠标导航 看到工作区
and see all the demos in this lesson.
并参阅本课中的所有演示
If you double-click on a file or on a folder,
如果双击文件或文件夹
it'll open and you can see the files there.
它会打开 你可以看到那里的文件
If you go to the "Back" button,
如果你按 后退 (Back) 按钮
it'll take you to where you were before,
它会把你带到之前的地方
and you can just navigate it like anything you're probably used to on your computer.
你可以像你常用的电脑习惯一样导航它
If you right-click, you'll see some options like,
如果你右键点击 你会看到一些选项
"Open," "Move," which is to move a file to
打开 (Open)  移动 (Move) 即移动文件
a different folder "Rename," "Copy," "Download," "Delete."
到一个不同的文件夹 还有 重命名  复制 下载 删除
And then, this "Plus" button is if you want to add a file,
这个 “Plus” 按钮的使用情景是 添加一个文件
add a folder, or upload something from your desktop that you were doing.
添加一个文件夹 或从你的桌面上上传你正在做的事情
Notice here, it says, "All changes saved."
注意这里的提示 所有的更改已被保存
So, everything you're doing here it just gets saved automatically.
即 你在这里所做的一切会被自动保存
Anything you type in this part will get saved automatically,
任何你在这部分输入的内容都会自动保存
and so you don't have to worry about saving things.
所以你不必担心保存的东西
This part right here is a text editor.
在这里的部分是一个文本编辑器
So, you can see this instructions.md file is really a text file that
你可以看到 instructions.md 文件是一个真正的文本文件
explains what the demo is and then here you have machine code.cpp,
它解释了演示是什么 然后在这里你有 machine code.cpp
which is a C++ file.
这是一个C ++文件
You can actually close these files,
实际上你可以关闭这些文件
open these files by double-clicking over here,
双击这里 打开这些文件
it works kind of like your regular computer.
它的工作方式就像你的普通电脑
So, then, the next part is this big chunk down here where it says,
下一个部分就是这个大块头
"New Terminal, No Open Terminals."
“新终端  没有开放的终端”
So, this is where you're actually going to be able
这是你实际上能够
to write commands directly to this remote computer.
将命令直接写入此远程计算机的地方
So, if I click on "New Terminal" here or on this "Plus" sign,
如果我点击这里或 “Plus” 上的 “New Terminal”（新终端）
it's going to open this New Window.
将打开这个新窗口
So, here it says, home/workspace.
这里提示 主页/工作区
So, that tells me that I'm actually here in the workspace folder.
这告诉我 我实际上是在工作区文件夹
As you click on this part versus this part,
当你点击这部分 和 这部分
they're actually not connected.
它们实际上没有连接
So, if you want to navigate different folders in the terminal,
如果你想在终端中导航不同的文件夹
you have to actually put commands in to do that.
你必须真的把命令放在那里
The instructions actually talk about and give you the commands that you're going to need.
说明实际上是给你 你将需要的命令
So, don't worry too much about that.
所以 不用太担心
So, I'm going to go through an example of how you can use this to run your C++ code.
我将通过一个如何使用它来运行C ++代码的例子 来详细介绍
Every time this opens for you in the classroom,
每次它在教室里为你打开
you're going to see this instruction file,
你会看到这个说明文件
and it's going to tell you exactly what you need to type in down here and in what order.
它会告诉你到底需要输入什么内容以及按什么顺序输入
You can either just go here and copy these commands,
你可以在这里复制这些命令
and copy and paste them,
并复制粘贴它们
and they'll just show up and then you hit "Return" and they'll run,
它们会出现 然后你点击“Return” 会启动运行
or alternatively, you can type them out.
或者 你可以自己输入它们
So, without worrying too much about what all of these commands do,
不用担心所有的这些命令做了什么
type this in, I'm saying, CD, change directory.
键入这个 我指的是 CD 改变目录(change directory)
So now, you can see that in the terminal,
现在 你可以看到 在终端
I've changed folders and I'm inside this demo_machine_code folder.
我已经改变了文件夹 在这个 demo_machine_code 文件夹里面
And then, this next code here,
然后 这里的下一个代码
it is going to compile my C++.
它将会编译我的 C ++
Okay, and then, you can see over here, this.o file appeared,
然后 你可以在这里看到这个 .o 文件出现了
and then it says in the instructions to type this out,
然后在说明中说明输入
and this is the results of the demo.
这是演示的结果
And if you read through the ReadMe file or this instructions file,
如果你通读 Readme 文件或该说明文件
you'll understand what all this is doing.
你会明白这一切在做什么
The other part I wanted to mention is this menu down here.
我想提到的另一部分是这里的菜单
So, if this freezes for some reason and it just isn't running right,
所如果由于某种原因而卡住 而且运行不正确
you can always hit "Refresh Workspace" down here.
你可以随时在这里点击“刷新工作区(Refresh Workspace)”
It's just going to reconnect.
这只是要重新连接
Your work will be the same everything is saved but it just let's you start over again.
你的工作将是一切都保存 但它只是让你重新开始
If you want to reset everything and get
如果你想重置一切
back to the original code that we provided for you,
回到我们为你提供的原始代码
you'll have to click on "Reset Data," which opens this Window here,
你可以点击 “Reset Data” (重置代码) 在这里打开这个窗口
and it says "Resetting data will wipe
它会提示 “重置数据将清除原有数据“
all of your work to restore the project to the original
所有的工作恢复到原来的项目
state" and then you type in "Reset Data" and click.
然后输入”重置数据“并单击。
I really suggest that you do not reset the data unless you
我真的建议你不要重置数据
have saved all of your work externally and downloaded it because,
除非你已经保存了所有的并下载了它
for example, if you just want to reset
例如 如果你只是想重置
these files and you hit "Reset Data," it's going to reset everything,
这些文件 你点击“重置数据” 这将重置一切
and you're going to lose all of your work.
你会失去所有现有的数据
So, make sure that if you need to
如果你需要 请确保
reset the data that you have right-clicked on everything and you've
重置右键单击所有内容的数据
downloaded all your code to the desktop or to wherever
并提前将所有代码下载到桌面或任何地方
so that you can then upload it again after you've restarted things.
以便在重新启动之后再重新上传
Again, every single one of these lessons,
再次提醒 每一节课中
like Demo Binary over here,
都会出现像这样的工作区练习
it opens the files for you and gives you instructions and tells you what to do,
它为你打开文件 并给你说明 并告诉你该怎么做
and if you want to see the code that is related to all of this,
如果你想看到与所有这些相关的代码
you just click here "Demo Binary" and you've got the instructions file and main.cpp.
你只需点击这里“演示二进制 (Demo Binary)” 你会得到说明文件和main.cpp
So again, what you'll always be doing is you'll be opening this up,
再次提醒 你需要做的是打开这个
you'll be reading the instructions,
阅读说明
you'll open a new terminal,
打开一个新终端
you'll type these commands one at a time,
一次输入一行命令
hit "Enter" and everything will run.
点击“Enter” 一切都会运行
I am going to provide a link about what all of
我将提供一个链接
these commands are and what you can do but it's not something that you need right now.
包含这些命令是 你可以做什么 但这不是你现在需要的东西。
But if you want to study it more and see how you can use
不过 如果你想更多的研究 看看你可以如何使用终端
the terminal not only in the classroom but using it for yourself on your computer,
不仅在教室里 而且在你的电脑上使用它
it's something that is really helpful,
这是非常有用的资源
and it's something that a lot of software engineers need to be able to do. So, thanks.
这是很多软件工程师需要做的 谢谢听课